Leave Chinatown to follow me
and you shall live.
Otherwise, you shall die.
Since the bloody battle at Chinatown,
security has been tightened.
The eradication of rogues
has been accelerated.
The era of territorial rivalry is over.
Long, Phong, Ba
withdrew from the criminal world
according to the wish of Hung Chinatown.
The gangland at that time was a calm lake.
Until someone tries to stir it up.
The blood debt must be paid with blood.
A storm coming from The North Port
stirs Chinatown once more.
Ba!
[Revenge]
Give Ba back to me!
Brothers forever.
Any updates on Ky?
All gateways have been raided.
I think he's not out of town yet.
Call Kim to ask if she knows anything.
I will.
What do you want?
How dare you took Hai Cuong's side?
Since the train station's matter,
you've been taking my compliance
for granted.
You want to kill me?
You won't be able to flee
even if you kill me.
Then let's die together.
Nobody answered.
I wonder if something's happened.
Don't kill me.
I can help you.
Recently, a drug ring has been dismantled
with a large amount of goods.
As per preliminary information,
Le Quy Ky is believed to be the leader.
However, according to the project
committee, there is still a suspect behind…
[Duong Van Ba, Date of Birth: 1970]
[Peacefully passed away in 2000
at the age of 30 years old]
We will exact justice on you, Ba.
This is my fight.
I don't want to involve everyone.
I must take revenge.
I'll leave Chinatown to you guys this time.
No.
This is all ours.
Not yours only.
I owe you guys this time.
I will never forget this.
Big brother.
We want to join Chinatown again.
Are you sure?
The blood debt must be paid with blood.
[Lieutenant Duong Van Hung]
It's done, ma'am.
- Here.
- Okay, thank you.
Ms. Kim?
Oh, you.
Where are you heading to?
Oh, I have a business nearby.
It seems like you're working hard.
It's my job.
It's been a long time
I didn't see you come over.
I'm pretty busy lately.
I'll visit you when I have time.
Okay, I have to go now.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Excuse me!
- Yes, ma'am?
Where is the toilet?
This way, ma'am.
Should I pee here?
[Ky is traveling Southern...]
Afraid of me running away?
[Hai Cuong]
What's wrong?
[Ky is traveling Southern to escape
to Cambodia. Help me.]
Gather everybody here for me.
I'm listening.
Look this way.
Okay, done. Please wait for a while.
Hien. Follow the plan.
Yes.
Hao!
You must stay,
in case something goes wrong.
Oh no.
I remember putting the phone here,
but where has it gone?
Finish it.
Kim.
You're pretty,
and sexy like this.
It would be better if you were obedient.
I'll do it.
Phong.
Long.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let me.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
Take care of my mom.
Phong! Phong!
Kim!
Hold on! Hold on!
Hey! Running away?
Hien!
Big Brother!
Catch him!
Don't let him escape.
Fuck you bastard.
Long!
Fuck you!
- Let go of me!
- You're killing him!
I'll kill him!
I must take revenge for Ba!
You'll go to jail if he dies!
The image of the altar is not even decent.
Don't joke around.
I bet he would like it better
if I joked around.
Where do you think he is now?
In heaven, of course.
Nope.
He's in my heart.
[End]
Hai Cuong was blindsided by hatred,
that caused us to lose a big catch.
So the leader has escaped?
He hasn't been caught yet.
Ky is nothing but a front to sale drugs.
The whole ring belongs to one man.
Six Knots.
How about Chinatown?
Peaceful for now.
But we can't predict what will happen next.
[6 years later]
Dad, I want to be a
gangster when I grow up.
Hey, don’t be silly.
Listen, gangster is a one-way road.
You cannot turn around once you enter it.
Am I right, Hung?
Why are you keeping me
wearing this wig? It's hot like hell.
Well, the wig makes
you look like your father.
Just think of it as a hat.